Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
=Lust and Lies=
=الشهوة والكذب=
Get rid of that warehouse at once.
تخلص من هذا المستودع على الفور.
I don't want
أنا لا أريد
to get threatened again.
لتعرض للتهديد مرة أخرى.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
However,
لكن،
this storeroom matters a lot to Young Marshal Huo.
هذا المخزن له أهمية كبيرة بالنسبة للمارشال الشاب هيو.
I'm afraid
انا خائف
it's not easy to deal with it.
ليس من السهل التعامل معه.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
I dare you to move them!
أتحداك أن تحركهم!
No one
لا احد
gets to mess with this storeroom,
يتدخل في هذا المخزن،
including Governor!
بما فيهم المحافظ!
Get lost!
اغرب عن وجهي!
=Episode 15=
=الحلقة 15=
♪It's you in the blur of light and shadow♪
♪أنت في ضباب الضوء والظل♪
♪Our first encounter left me in awe for a lifetime♪
♪لقد تركني لقاءنا الأول في حالة من الرهبة مدى الحياة♪
Aren't you always curious about my secret?
هل أنت دائما فضولي بشأن سري؟
♪Feelings I can't shake off♪
♪مشاعر لا أستطيع التخلص منها♪
♪Quietly emerge♪
♪الظهور بهدوء♪
Did you know?
هل تعلم؟
They all say my mother killed herself.
كلهم يقولون أن أمي قتلت نفسها.
But I saw
ولكنني رأيت
him killing her.
قتلها.
♪Sweet words exist only in dreams♪
♪الكلمات الحلوة موجودة فقط في الأحلام♪
♪Memories are like faded negatives♪
♪الذكريات مثل السلبيات الباهتة♪
♪Replaying endlessly♪
♪إعادة تشغيل بلا نهاية♪
Mother!
الأم!
Let go of me!
أتركني!
Ever since my mother went mad,
منذ أن أصيبت والدتي بالجنون،
she'd been locked up in here.
لقد تم حبسها هنا.
She was locked up here for five years.
لقد تم حبسها هنا لمدة خمس سنوات.
So Mother was paying respect to your mother
فكانت الأم تحترم والدتك
in the mountain.
في الجبل.
But I only dared pay respect to her in secret.
ولكنني لم أجرؤ على إظهار احترامي لها إلا في السر.
Sometimes I'd stay her for some time
أحيانًا كنت أبقى معها لبعض الوقت
until the incense went off.
حتى ذهب البخور.
I don't want to lose you.
لا أريد أن أخسرك.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
you're all I have.
أنت كل ما أملك.
Don't you ever leave me.
لا تتركني أبدًا.
And don't betray me.
ولا تخونني
Are we having a deal here?
هل لدينا صفقة هنا؟
I entrust my life to you.
أسلم حياتي إليك.
♪Do you remember the sound of the flute in the wind?♪
♪هل تتذكر صوت الناي في الريح؟♪
♪It whispers of the flame we shared♪
♪همس من اللهب الذي شاركناه♪
I hope
آمل
this fire will burn the entire residence.
هذه النار سوف تحرق المنزل بأكمله.
Wenyan...
وينيان...
Wenyan!
وينيان!
It's on fire!
إنها تحترق!
The storeroom is on fire!
المخزن يحترق!
Help!
يساعد!
Governor.
محافظ.
Tell them to forget about it.
اطلب منهم أن ينسوا هذا الأمر.
I was going to get rid of it
كنت سأتخلص منه
after all.
بعد كل شيء.
Miss Qingwan did it.
لقد فعلتها السيدة تشينغوان.
How reckless of you!
كم أنت متهور!
I acted rather recklessly
لقد تصرفت بتهور إلى حد ما
to make the Governor believe that I don't harbor any ill thoughts.
لجعل الحاكم يعتقد أنني لا أحمل أي أفكار سيئة.
I'm just trying to ease his burden.
أنا فقط أحاول تخفيف العبء عنه.
Moreover, that storeroom
علاوة على ذلك، هذا المخزن
always bothered him.
لقد أزعجته دائمًا.
It was his weakness too.
لقد كان ضعفه أيضاً.
Someone had to get rid of it for him.
كان لابد على شخص ما أن يتخلص منه من أجله.
Mother.
الأم.
You fought with Governor for times because of me.
لقد حاربت مع الحاكم عدة مرات بسببي.
Only when I gain a foothold
فقط عندما أحصل على موطئ قدم
can I protect you.
هل يمكنني حمايتك؟
In this family,
في هذه العائلة،
you need to learn
أنت بحاجة إلى التعلم
how to protect yourself first.
كيفية حماية نفسك أولاً
Got it, Mother.
فهمت يا أمي.
Miss.
يفتقد.
Governor asked for your presence in the army headquarters.
لقد طلب المحافظ حضوركم في مقر الجيش.
Please.
لو سمحت.
Careful, Miss.
احذري يا آنسة.
Governor,
محافظ،
Miss Qingwan is here.
السيدة تشينغوان هنا.
Aren't you scared?
ألا تخافين؟
I believe
انا أؤمن
you won't kill me.
لن تقتلني
Why?
لماذا؟
It's because all fathers love their children.
لأن جميع الآباء يحبون أبناءهم
Don't kill me!
لا تقتلني!
Governor.
محافظ.
Miss Qingwan is nowhere to be seen.
لم يتم رؤية السيدة تشينغوان في أي مكان.
Do we keep setting fire on it?
هل نستمر في إشعال النار فيه؟
(Qingwan.)
(تشينغوان.)
(Don't blame me.)
(لا تلوموني.)
(Find yourself a good family in the next lifetime.)
(ابحث عن عائلة جيدة في حياتك القادمة.)
After everything I've done in the past few days,
بعد كل ما فعلته في الأيام القليلة الماضية،
don't you resent me?
ألا تستاء مني؟
It's all thanks to you
كل هذا بفضلك
that I'm now free of the Huofeng Gang's control.
أنني الآن حر من سيطرة عصابة هووفينج.
Father, I just want you...
أبي، أريدك فقط...
Governor, I just want you to be safe and sound.
السيد المحافظ، أريد فقط أن تكون سالمًا معافى.
If you want to call me Father,
إذا كنت تريد أن تناديني بأبي،
just do it.
افعل ذلك.
You've been wandering around since you were young.
لقد كنت تتجول منذ أن كنت صغيرا.
I haven't taught you anything.
لم أعلمك شيئا.
Today,
اليوم،
I shall teach you how to use a gun.
سأعلمك كيفية استخدام السلاح.
Father...
أب...
Bear this in mind.
ضع هذا في الاعتبار.
Don't ever let someone point a gun to you.
لا تسمح أبدًا لأحد أن يوجه إليك مسدسًا.
Unless you're good enough to put up a fight.
إلا إذا كنت جيدًا بما يكفي لخوض القتال.
Here.
هنا.
Afraid not.
لا أخاف.
One.
واحد.
Two.
اثنين.
Three.
ثلاثة.
Shoot.
أطلق النار.
Father!
أب!
I've got it, Father!
لقد حصلت عليه يا أبي!
Governor.
محافظ.
Qingwan.
تشينغوان.
Head back and get some rest.
عد إلى الوراء واحصل على بعض الراحة.
Thank you, Governor.
شكرا لك يا سيدي المحافظ.
Today's the happiest day in my life.
اليوم هو أسعد يوم في حياتي.
Call me Father.
ناديني يا أبي.
Thank you, Father.
شكرا لك يا أبي.
She knows how to shoot a gun.
إنها تعرف كيفية إطلاق النار.
She'd have hid the fact that she knows how to use a gun
لقد كانت ستخفي حقيقة أنها تعرف كيفية استخدام السلاح
or pretended she can't hold one steady
أو تظاهرت بأنها لا تستطيع أن تثبت واحدة
or even fired a near miss.
أو حتى أطلقت النار على هدف قريب.
She would never hit the bullseye.
انها لن تصل الى عين الثور ابدًا.
She's my daughter.
إنها ابنتي.
Huo Qingwan.
هوو تشينغوان.
♪Listen, the bell rings from afar♪
♪استمع، الجرس يرن من بعيد♪
♪The fog lifts, your image still hazy♪
♪يرتفع الضباب، وصورتك لا تزال ضبابية♪
♪Do you remember the sound of the flute in the wind?♪
♪هل تتذكر صوت الناي في الريح؟♪
♪It whispers of the flame we shared♪
♪همس من اللهب الذي شاركناه♪
♪Having seen those prophecies left behind♪
♪بعد أن رأيت تلك النبوءات التي تركوها وراءهم♪
♪A sudden will to survive arises♪
♪تنشأ فجأة رغبة في البقاء♪
♪The ruan resounds with grandeur♪
♪الروان يتردد صداه بالعظمة♪
♪Under the pelting plum rain♪
♪تحت المطر الغزير من البرقوق♪
♪Everyone sings the final act♪
♪الجميع يغني الفصل الأخير♪
♪All fading away♪
♪كل شيء يتلاشى♪
♪The curtain falls♪
♪الستار يسقط♪